<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About Me on Brandon Liang</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/</link><description>Recent content in About Me on Brandon Liang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brandonliang.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hackathons</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/hackathons/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/hackathons/</guid><description>Hackathons aren&amp;rsquo;t an obligation, they&amp;rsquo;re a lifestyle. Every in-person hackathon I&amp;rsquo;ve attended has been an opportunity to learn, meet smart people at different universities, visit a new city, enjoy great food, and check out the hottest new technologies.
Before the pandemic, I would travel to a hackathon once every other weekend. Now that I&amp;rsquo;m close to graduation, my lifestyle is coming to an end.
Here is my Devpost.
My final planned hackathon is Hack&amp;amp;Roll in Singapore in January 2023!</description></item><item><title>New Grad Finale: 2023</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/finale-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/finale-2023/</guid><description>New Grad Finale: 2023 Read the 2022 prequel [here]
Northeastern has a co-op program where upperclassmen spend 4-8 months working full-time instead of taking classes for a semester. Eventually though, I need to graduate and start working full-time for real. So how does it all end?
The Application Process Applied: 71
Interviews/OAs: 28
Withdrawn: 2
Offers: 4
TODO&amp;hellip;
The end, at least for now</description></item><item><title>&lt;&lt; System Announcement >></title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/system-announcement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/system-announcement/</guid><description>Welcome to my world. My name is Akihiko Kayaba. And as of this moment, I am in control of this world. I&amp;rsquo;m sure most of you have already noticed an item missing from your main menus: the logout button. Let me ensure you, this is not a defect in the game. I repeat&amp;hellip; This is not a defect, this is how Sword Art Online was designed to be. You cannot log yourselves out of SAO.</description></item><item><title>Returning to Yu-Gi-Oh</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/yugioh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/yugioh/</guid><description>Last modified on: 2022-08-22
I got back into Yu-Gi-Oh! recently with the iOS release of Master Duel and have built three different decks for competitive play. The highest tier I&amp;rsquo;ve made it to as of this writing is Platinum I (after Diamond rank update).
Swordsoul Tenyi TODO
D/D/D &amp;ldquo;D/D/D&amp;rdquo; stands for Different Dimension Daemon. Taste the power of demon kings that have conquered different dimensions.
It&amp;rsquo;s an incredibly hard deck to master, and I still am in the process of doing so.</description></item><item><title>Co-op Duels: 2022</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2022/</guid><description>Co-op Duels: 2022 Last modified on: 2022-11-25
Read the 2021 prequel [here]
Recruiting sucked the soul out of me late-September to mid-October Northeastern has a co-op program where upperclassmen spend 4-8 months working full-time instead of taking classes for a semester, here&amp;rsquo;s how it went during my junior year.
I interned as a software engineer at Snowflake in Boston working on diagnostics reporting, followed by Duolingo in Pittsburgh working on speech recognition, followed by Meta in NYC working on augmented reality headsets.</description></item><item><title>Semester Abroad in Switzerland</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/switzerland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/switzerland/</guid><description>Last modified on: 2022-12-03
The town of Lucerne During the Fall 2021 semester, I studied computer science as an exchange student at the University of Zürich and a special student at ETH Zürich in Switzerland. Here&amp;rsquo;s how it went.
(Most of this content is readapted from my exchange experience report, thanks goes to my friend Elaine for helping me edit this.)
Preparing Accepted for a exchange! I applied to UZH through Northeastern’s Global Experience Office.</description></item><item><title>Travel</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/travel/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/projects/</guid><description>See some of the best projects I&amp;rsquo;ve done as a student! AR Quiz It's an augmented reality scavenger hunt. We made a quiz game in Unity where each question prompts you to find a QR in a specific room, which when scanned, renders a 3d object that answers the question (try this one 😉)! [Demo] EAST It stands for "Endangered Animal Species Tracker". Edge computing using drones is an emerging technology I wanted to try out to write such an application.</description></item><item><title>Thoughts</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/thoughts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/thoughts/</guid><description>My Thoughts Just a collection of thoughts and interesting questions I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about. If you have answers or an opinion to these, I&amp;rsquo;d love to start a conversation!
Restart Civilization Suppose every human on Earth suddenly disappears except you and the other people at your university or workplace. What is the first thing you and your friends do? In the long-term, how would this event affect race, religion, and politics?</description></item><item><title>Co-op Duels: 2021</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2021/</guid><description>Co-op Duels: 2021 Last modified on: 2022-11-25
Northeastern has a co-op program where upperclassmen spend 4-8 months working full-time instead of taking classes for a semester, this is how it went during my sophomore year. Some people opt for one long co-op, some break it up into two (me), and some even three.
I interned as a software engineer at MathWorks working on the MATLAB engine, followed by Microsoft working on the Azure cloud computing platform, respectively.</description></item><item><title>My First Post!</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/my-first-post/</guid><description>I decided to migrate from my old website to a blog on the Hugo engine, since I feel like writing to capture my unconventional college experience. My university friend Josh also gave me some great advice to change to a minimalistic website as I&amp;rsquo;d get tired of the design less easily.</description></item></channel></rss>