<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About Me on Brandon Liang</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/</link><description>Recent content in About Me on Brandon Liang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brandonliang.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Semester Abroad in Switzerland</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/switzerland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/switzerland/</guid><description>The town of Lucerne During the Fall 2021 semester, I studied computer science as an exchange student at the University of Zürich and a special student at ETH Zürich in Switzerland. Here&amp;rsquo;s how it went.
(Most of this content is readapted from my exchange experience report, thanks goes to my friend Elaine for helping me edit this.)
Preparing Accepted for a exchange! I applied to UZH through Northeastern’s Global Experience Office.</description></item><item><title>Hackathons</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/hackathons/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/hackathons/</guid><description>Hackathons aren&amp;rsquo;t just an obligation for me, they&amp;rsquo;re a lifestyle. Why do I enjoy them so much? Every hackathon I&amp;rsquo;ve attended has been an opportunity to learn, meet smart people at different universities, visit a new city, enjoy great food, and check out the hottest new technologies.
Before the pandemic, I would travel to a hackathon once every other weekend. Here are just a few I have on my wishlist before I graduate college:</description></item><item><title>Travel</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/travel/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/projects/</guid><description>Have a look at some the best projects I&amp;rsquo;ve done in my developer career! EAST It stands for "Endangered Animal Species Tracker". Edge computing using drones is an emerging technology I wanted to try out to write such an application. Video footage is forwarded from a drone to an RCNN trained with transfer learning for live object detection on animals! Sign Friendly It's difficult for the deaf to communicate with sign language, but this becomes harder cross-culturally because each language carries its own set of sign language gestures.</description></item><item><title>Thoughts</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/thoughts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/thoughts/</guid><description>My Thoughts Just a collection of thoughts and interesting questions I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about. If you have answers or an opinion to these, I&amp;rsquo;d love to start a conversation!
Restart Civilization Suppose every human on Earth suddenly disappears except you and the other people at your university or workplace. What is the first thing you and your friends do? In the long-term, how would this event affect race, religion, and politics?</description></item><item><title>Co-op Quest: 2021</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2021/</guid><description>Co-op Quest: 2021 Northeastern has a co-op program where upperclassmen spend 4-8 months working full-time instead of taking classes for a semester, this is how it went during my sophomore year. Some people opt for one long co-op, some break it up into two (me), and some even three.
I interned as a software engineer at MathWorks working on the MATLAB engine, followed by Microsoft working on the Azure cloud computing platform, respectively.</description></item><item><title>My First Post!</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/my-first-post/</guid><description>I decided to migrate from my old website to a blog on the Hugo engine, since I feel like writing to capture my unconventional college experience. My university friend Josh also gave me some great advice to change to a minimalistic website as I&amp;rsquo;d get tired of the design less easily.</description></item></channel></rss>