<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Brandon Liang</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Brandon Liang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brandonliang.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Semester Abroad in Switzerland</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/switzerland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/switzerland/</guid><description>The town of Lucerne During the Fall 2021 semester, I studied computer science as an exchange student at the University of Zürich and a special student at ETH Zürich in Switzerland. Here&amp;rsquo;s how it went.
(Most of this content is readapted from my exchange experience report)
Preparing Accepted for a exchange! I applied to UZH through Northeastern’s Global Experience Office. I was interested in Swiss universities for their strong rankings in computer science and finance.</description></item><item><title>Travel</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/travel/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Co-op Quest: 2021</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2021/</guid><description>Co-op Quest: 2021 Northeastern has a co-op program where upperclassmen spend 4-8 months working full-time instead of taking classes for a semester, this is how it went during my sophomore year. Some people opt for one long co-op, some break it up into two (me), and some even three.
I interned as a software engineer at MathWorks working on the MATLAB engine, followed by Microsoft working on the Azure cloud computing platform, respectively.</description></item><item><title>My First Post!</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/my-first-post/</guid><description>I decided to migrate from my old website to a blog on the Hugo engine, since I feel like writing to capture my unconventional college experience. My university friend Josh also gave me some great advice to change to a minimalistic website as I&amp;rsquo;d get tired of the design less easily.</description></item></channel></rss>