<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Brandon Liang</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Brandon Liang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brandonliang.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Returning to Yu-Gi-Oh</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/yugioh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/yugioh/</guid><description>Last modified on: 2022-08-22
I got back into Yu-Gi-Oh! recently with the iOS release of Master Duel and have built three different decks for competitive play. The highest tier I&amp;rsquo;ve made it to as of this writing is Platinum I (after Diamond rank update).
Swordsoul Tenyi TODO
D/D/D &amp;ldquo;D/D/D&amp;rdquo; stands for Different Dimension Daemon. Taste the power of demon kings that have conquered different dimensions.
It&amp;rsquo;s an incredibly hard deck to master, and I still am in the process of doing so.</description></item><item><title>Co-op Duels: 2022</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2022/</guid><description>Co-op Duels: 2022 Last modified on: 2022-09-30 Read the 2021 prequel [here]
Northeastern has a co-op program where upperclassmen spend 4-8 months working full-time instead of taking classes for a semester, here&amp;rsquo;s how it went during my junior year.
I interned as a software engineer at Snowflake in Boston working on diagnostics reporting, followed by Duolingo in Pittsburgh working on speech recognition, followed by Meta in NYC working on augmented reality headsets.</description></item><item><title>Semester Abroad in Switzerland</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/switzerland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/switzerland/</guid><description>The town of Lucerne During the Fall 2021 semester, I studied computer science as an exchange student at the University of Zürich and a special student at ETH Zürich in Switzerland. Here&amp;rsquo;s how it went.
(Most of this content is readapted from my exchange experience report, thanks goes to my friend Elaine for helping me edit this.)
Preparing Accepted for a exchange! I applied to UZH through Northeastern’s Global Experience Office.</description></item><item><title>Travel</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/travel/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Co-op Duels: 2021</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/recruiting-2021/</guid><description>Co-op Duels: 2021 Last modified on: 2022-08-22
Northeastern has a co-op program where upperclassmen spend 4-8 months working full-time instead of taking classes for a semester, this is how it went during my sophomore year. Some people opt for one long co-op, some break it up into two (me), and some even three.
I interned as a software engineer at MathWorks working on the MATLAB engine, followed by Microsoft working on the Azure cloud computing platform, respectively.</description></item><item><title>My First Post!</title><link>https://brandonliang.com/blog/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonliang.com/blog/my-first-post/</guid><description>I decided to migrate from my old website to a blog on the Hugo engine, since I feel like writing to capture my unconventional college experience. My university friend Josh also gave me some great advice to change to a minimalistic website as I&amp;rsquo;d get tired of the design less easily.</description></item></channel></rss>